어지러운 전국 시대.
It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over
Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
Karakuri martial artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri martial artist!
무사시 등장이오!
Musashi is here-dasu!
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden
Musashi Road
(The Story of Karakuri Martial Artist: Road of Musashi)
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
A man always dreams of the day
제일 강해질 날을
in the center of the world to become
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
AH! AH! the strongest
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
모험의 길의 막을 연다
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes a life dazzle
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
내일은 빛난다
Tomorrow will be glorious
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes a life dazzle
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Fight the utmost with the stillness
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
His eyes shined! Musashi!!
지팡구 무예대회에 나가지 못하고 번외 시합에선 주베에게 완패당하는 것으로 모자라 한조에게 잡혀버리고 만
Not only he wasn't able to participate in the martial arts competition, but he also lost to Jūbē in an extra match;
he was even captured by Hanzo. All the misfortunes had come at once,
엎친 데 덮친 격이었던 무사시는 이번엔 날뛰는 말과 같은 센히메를 모시고 따라가며 여러 지방을 돌아다니게 되었다.
and as they went away, Musashi now have to follow Senhime and wander around various places.
큰 두꺼비 요술 지라이얀이오
Giant Toad Magic
Jiraiyan
지팡구의 아침이 갠 이 날, 무사시, 코지로, 센히메가 여행을 떠나는 날이었다.
This day, the sun has rose, and Musashi, Kojirō, and Senhime will go for a journey.
작은 새가 이렇게나...
So many small birds...
정말 대단합니다.
Truly wonderful.
고마워.
Thank you!
그래도 정말, 무사시 놈 늦는군!
Nonetheless, Musashi is being really late!
늦잠이라도 자나?
Is he sleeping or something?
뭐, 괜찮잖아?
It doesn't matter, does it?
아, 왔다!
Hey, he's here!
기다리셨소!
I'm finally here-dasu!
출발하오!
Let's go-dasu!
어이! 지각한 주제에 뭔 소리냐!
Hey! For being late, you shouldn't say that.
조금 늦은 정도가지고 그러오...
I'm only a little bit late-dasu...
센히메의 방위 역은 나. 넌 조수다. 잊지 마라!
I guard Senhime, and you're only an assistant! Do not forget!
알고 있소.
I know-dasu.
그럼! 남쪽으로 출발하오!
Then! Let's go to the south!
뭔 소리냐! 북이다!
What's wrong with you? To the north!
남이오!
It's south-dasu!
북이다.
It's north.
남이라면 남이오!
If I say it's south, then it's south-dasu!
절대 북이다!
It is north no matter what!
이럇!
Here!
앞면이면 북, 뒷면이면 남이야.
To north if front side, and to south if back side.
고마워.
Thank you.
무사시, 불만 없지?
Musashi, I hope you have no objection!
그렇소...
Right-dasu...
센히메 님, 삼국, 아니, 지팡구 제일의 새신랑을 찾아 오십시오.
Senhime, I hope you will find the best husband in the three county - no, in the Jipangu!
고마워, 주베. 힘낼게.
Thank you, Jūbē. I'll try.
북쪽 지방에는 그 정체를 알 수 없는 괴물이 악행을 저지르고 있다는 정보가 있습니다.
I have an information that an unknown monster is doing bad things in the north.
어떤 괴물이 나온다 하더라도 괜찮소! 내가 픽픽 쓰러지게 만들어 주겠소!
It doesn't matter no matter what kind of monster come out-dasu! I'll get rid of them at once-dasu!
그 기세다, 무사시!
That's the spirit, Musashi!
무사시 씨라면 괜찮아. 그 배에 붙은 귀신에 괴물도 놀아 달아날 게다!
Mr. Musashi will do! That monster in his stomach will shoo away those monsters.
그렇소! 내게 맡기시오!
That's right-dasu! Leave it to me-dasu!
그럼 여러분, 다녀올게요.
Then everyone, see you!
아, 잠깐! 기다리시오!
Hey, wait for me-dasu!
이건 앞이 훤하군... 별 일 없으면 좋겠는데.
I see where this is going. I hope nothing happen to them...
다시 어디선가 만나자!
See you again somewhere!
무사시 형, 조심해!
Musashi brother, be careful!
너무 먹어서 배탈이나 나지 마라!
Don't make your stomach upset after eating too much!
기다리시오!
Wait for me-dasu!
센히메 일행이 북쪽으로 출발했습니다.
Senhime and fellow people are heading to the north.
흥.
Uh-huh.
일단은 인바 늪 근처가 노리는 곳. 카라쿠리 부엉이여, 우리 한조 부하 사천왕 중 하나, 지라이얀에게 가라.
We're keeping an eye on Inba Swamp. Karakuri Owl, go to Jiraiyan, one of the four kings of Hanzo.
센히메는 제너럴 이에야스의 약점. 이걸 붙잡으면 이에야스는 이 배후에 있는 한조 마음대로.
Senhime is the weak point of General Ieyasu. If I get to catch her, Ieyasu will fall into my hands.
많은 사람들이 돌아다니고 있네.
Many people are traveling!
예. 대부분은 나리타 템플에 참배하러 가는 것이겠지요.
Yes. I guess most of them are going to pray at Narita Temple.
어이. 딱딱한 이야기는 재미 없어.
Hey. Don't be so stiff!
무사시, 너도 들어.
Musashi, listen to me for a moment.
네네네네!
Right, right!
단고 사오?
Are we buying dangos-dasu?
어이, 무사시! 이 여행은 관광 여행이 아니다! 공주님을 지켜야 한다는 사명을 잊었나!
Hey, Musashi! This journey is not a pleasure trip! Did you forget your mission to protect the princess?
알고 있소. 하나하나 잘난 척은.
I know-dasu. How self-important.
자, 들어 줘.
Hey, hey, listen to me.
둘 다 날 공주님이라고 부르지 않아줬으면 해.
I'd like if you two don't call me princess.
봐, 무사시하고 만났을 때처럼 센짱이라 부르면 돼.
Remember this? You can call me Sen-chan just like we first met!
센짱이오? 알겠소.
Sen-chan-dasu? Got it-dasu.
그런데 센짱은 어떤 남자가 취향이오?
By the way, Sen-chan, what kind of man is your preference-dasu?
무사시! 실례다!
Musashi! That's rude!
취향을 알아야 상대를 구하기 쉽소!
It's easier to find a match only if we know her preference-dasu!
그렇네. 역시 잘생긴 사람이네.
Let's see... Of course, it's a handsome man!
잘생겼다고 하면... 나 말이구나!
A handsome man... that must be me!
그리고... 씩씩하고 강하고 마음은 곱고!
And... the one with resolute and strong body, and a tender mind!
강하고 마음 고운... 나 같소...
Strong and tender... that sounds like me-dasu...
어라?
Huh?
괜찮은 남자.
A good-looking man.
어, 공주님!
Hey, princess!
센짱, 저런 게 취향이오...
Sen-chan, is that your preference-dasu?...
여보!
Honey!
여보 기다렸소?
Did you wait for me?
아니, 별로!
No, not much!
가자, 코지로!
Let's go, Kojirō!
출항합니다!
We're departing!
기다리시오!
Wait for me!
또 꼴볼견이오!
I look pathetic again-dasu!
기다려 주소!
Wait for me-dasu!
뭐야?! 센히메 일행이? 그래, 오는구나!
What?! Senhime and her fellows? They're finally coming!
바보는 뭐오, 바보는!
What do you mean by that idiot-dasu?!
배에서 떨어지다니, 그게 멍청한 것이겠다!
To fall from a ship is a big stupidity!
더는 용서 못하오! 여기서 끝장을 내오!
I cannot forgive anymore-dasu! We'll finish this here-dasu!
해봤자.
Even if we did so.
아니오! 대체 내가 네 조수라는 건 마음에 안 드오!
No! I cannot accept being an assistant of you-dasu!
배에서 떨어진 바보. 그런 쉽게 열받는 이성적이지 못한 사내에게 공주를 지킨다는 중요한 일이 가능하다 생각하나!
An idiot that fell down from a boat. Do you think that such an easily flaring up guy can
do an important mission of protecting the princess?!
강하다고 막말하지 마시오! 여기서 승부를 보오!
Do not talk rude just because you're strong-dasu! Let's settle this here right now-dasu!
그럴 필요는...
No need to...
재밌겠네.
It's gonna be interesting!
있잖아, 있잖아! 해봐!
Hey, hey, hey! Do it!
공주님! 아니, 센님.
Princess! No, Sen-dono.
코지로의 츠바메가에시, 보고 싶어!
I want to see your Tsubamegaeshi, Kojirō.
어때, 무사시?
Do you agree, Musashi?
바라던 바이오.
That's what I wanted-dasu.
아니, 그래도...
But still...
자! 그럼 여기서 단판승부야!
Then let there be a single match!
좋소! 오시오!
Agreed! You may come!
죽어도 모른다!
You might die in the battle!
내가 이기면 코지로, 네가 내 하인이 되시오!
If I win, Kojirō, you'll become my servant-dasu!
좋아. 지면 어쩔래?
Sure. What if you lose?
그 때는 물구나무서기든 다 벗고 춤추든 뭐든 하겠소!
Then I'll stand by hand, or get all the clothes off me and dance or something-dasu!
그 말, 잊지 마라!
Do not forget your words!
시작하오!
Here I go-dasu!
진짜, 달아나지 말고 착실히 싸우시오!
Really, don't run away and fight directly-dasu!
흥, 조금은 솜씨가 향상된 것 같구나.
Heh, it seems that you've gotten better for a bit.
이걸로 끝장이오!
This will finish-dasu!
훌륭해! 멋졌어.
Excellent! It was so cool!
황송합니다.
I am grateful.
무사시?
Musashi?
뭔 짓이냐!
What are you doing?!
약속대로이오!
As we promised!
알았어, 꼴볼견이니까 관둬!
Okay! That's already unseemly enough, so stop that!
싫소. 사내는 약속은 지키오!
No-dasu. A man will keep his promise-dasu!
오, 무사시의 근성, 다시 봤어!
Heh, I looked again at Musashi's guts!
힘내봐!
Keep it up!
뭔 일이 있어도 코지로 님의 조수는 싫다는 건가...
So I guess that you hate to be an assistant of Mr. Kojirō no matter what...
죽어도 싫소!
Even if I die-dasu!
마침 잘 됐군. 그 식사에는 독을 넣어 두었다.
That's great to know. I've placed poison in that meal.
도, 독?!
P- poison?!
으앙! 죽소! 죽소!
waaaaah! I'm dying! I'm dying!
는 것은 거짓말이다!
And that is a lie!
거짓말?
A lie?
너무하오!
That's cruel-dasu!
그건 그렇고, 무사시 님, 그 콩을 젓가락 하나로 집을 수 있는가?
Anyway, Mr. Musashi, can you pick up that bean with one chopstick?
어? 하나로?
Huh? With one?
젓가락 하나로는 무리이오...
It's impossible using only one-dasu...
그럼 둘이라면 어떤가.
Then how about two?
이거라면 쉽소.
This is easy-dasu.
그런 것입니다.
That's how it is.
그런 것?
That's how it is?
코지로 님에게 츠바메가에시라는 비검이 있다고 해도 그 칼은 하나.
Even if Mr. Kojirō has a secret sword named Tsubamegaeshi, he has one sword.
칼은 둘이 있다.
There are two swords.
이도류...
Dual blade...
언젠가 우연히 보여주신 이도류의 기술. 그 자세를 공부한다면 천하무적의 무예가가 될 지도 모릅니다.
Technique of dual blade that you showed me by chance.
If you explore about that posture, you might become the matchless Martial Artist as well.
이도류를 공부하는 것이겠소!
So I should study dual blade-dasu!
코지로 님과 함께 여행하면서 자신의 검술을 수련하며 이도류를 완성하는 건 어떨지요.
I suggest you to make your technique of dual blade excellent during the journey with Kojirō.
알겠소. 나, 꼭 이도류를 공부해서 숙명의 라이벌, 코지로를 쓰러뜨리겠소!
Understood-dasu. I will take Kojirō down by studying the technique of dual blade-dasu!
이도류를 완성한 새벽녘에는 이 괴물을 퇴치하십시오.
When you completed your technique of dual blade, you will eliminate these monsters.
야마타노오로치... 츠치구모...
Yamata no Orochi... Tsuchigumo...
그 괴물은 신이 다스리던 시대부터 명도 천공환, 천지환을 지키고 있다고 전해지는 괴물입니다.
They are the monsters that are told to be protecting the sacred swords named Tenkūmaru and Tenchimaru.
그 괴물을 퇴치하면 그 명도가 손에 들어오는 것이오!
So by getting rid of those monsters, I will be able to have those excellent swords!
그 때야말로 무사시 님은 천하제일의 검호가 되겠죠.
When that time comes, Mr. Musashi, you'll become the best of the master swordsmen in the world.
주베 씨, 감사하오!
Thank you so much, Mr. Jūbē-dasu!
나, 힘껏 해 보겠소!
I'll do that with all my might!
그렇소! 이도류를 완성하면 코지로에게 질 리가 없소!
That's it-dasu! When I complete my dual blade skills, I won't be losing to Kojirō-dasu!
이렇게 하면 되오!
This will do-dasu!
인바 늪에 커다란 두꺼비가 두껍두껍하고 울고 있었다.
In Inba swamp, a big toad was crying croak croak.
질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
센짱하고 코지로, 어디까지 간 것이오?
Where did Sen-chan and Kojirō go to-dasu?
좋은 냄새이오!
What a good smell-dasu!
아, 안되오! 나는 센히메 님을 지킨다는 지명과 이도류를 공부한다는 중요한 목적이 있소!
Ah, no-dasu! I have an important objective of protecting Senhime and study dual blade skills-dasu!
사내는 참소!
A man will control oneself-dasu!
어, 야, 무사시!
H- hey, Musashi!
어라, 무사시 가 버렸네.
Huh, Musashi went.
저 단고에 미친 놈이 참다니, 믿을 수가 없군!
I can't believe that dango-craving guy is actually enduring!
분명 책임감 때문일거야.
Must be his sense of responsibility.
남은 단고는 가지고 가자.
Let's bvring the leftover dangos.
예.
Right.
정말, 어디까지 폐를 끼칠 놈이냐.
Really, to what extent will he bother us?
저런, 무사시도 귀여운 면 있잖아.
You know, Musashi is cute too!
귀여... 저게... 요?
Cu... that... is?
그래! 그래서 흥미롭잖아?
Yeah! Isn't that interesting?
저기요! 남은 단고는 포장해 주세요!
Excuse me! Please wrap the leftover dangos!
내가 훨씬 잘생겼다 생각하지만...
I think I am a whole lot more handsome...
공주님 취향은 이해할 수 없군.
I can't understand the princess' preferences.
어라? 어쩐지 길을 잃은 것 같소.
Huh? It seems that I got lost-dasu.
왠지 기분 나쁜 곳이오... 가까이에 집도 없고.
What a creepy place-dasu... there's no house nearby, too...
저, 저런... 배 안에서 거지가 날뛰오...
Oh, those vermin in my stomach are raging-dasu...
날은 저물었고 곤란해졌소.
It got dark and I'm in trouble-dasu.
어라, 뭣이오?
What is this-dasu?!
나갈 수가 없소!
I can't get out-dasu!
으악! 누가 살려주시오!
waaah! Someone help me-dasu!
으악! 살려주시오!
waaaaaaaaaaah! Help me-dasu!
어, 무슨 소리오?
W- what is this sound-dasu?
으악! 안되겠소! 살려주시오!
waaah! It's no good-dasu! Help me!
살려주시오!
Help me!
어라, 무사시 목소리같아.
Hey, isn't that Musashi?
죽고 싶지 않소!
I do not want to die-dasu!
저쪽으로!
That way!
무사시!
Musashi!
죽소! 죽겠소!
I'm dying! I'm gonna die-dasu!
-무사시!
-Musashi!
여기이오! 빨리 살려주시오!
Here I am-dasu! Hurry up and help me!
무사시!
Musashi!
지옥에 떨어진다는 건 이걸 말하오!
Falling into the hell means this!
센히메 님을 방위할 네가 뭔 방해냐!
You should be protecting Senhime, not bother us!
면목없소.
I'm so sorry-dasu...
센히메! 기다리고 있다!
Senhime! I was waiting for you!
살았소... 뱃가죽이 등에 붙지만 않았으면 이런 바보짓은...
I'm saved-dasu... if I wasn't so hungry, I wouldn't have acted so stupidly...
자, 여기!
Here, for you!
우와! 먹어도 괜찮소?
Whoa! Can I eat them-dasu?
물론! 천천히 먹어.
Of course! Eat them slowly.
기쁘오.
I'm so happy-dasu.
맛있소!
So good-dasu.
정말... 네 덕분에 다음 역참까지 갈 수 없게 되어버렸다. 오늘은 여기서 노숙이야.
Really... thanks to you, we can't go to the next relay station. We'll sleep outdoors at here.
아니, 이것도 재밌잖아.
Hey, isn't this fun too?
공주님!
Princess!
센짱이라 불러!
Call me Sen-chan!
센짱!
S- Sen-chan!
무사시!
Musashi!
순순히 센히메를 넘겨라!
Obediently hand over Senhime!
그러지 않으면 이 늪의 바닥으로 가라앉혀주겠다!
Or else, I'll make you sink to the very bottom of this swamp!
닥치시오! 센짱은 이 무사시가 명을 걸고 지키오!
Shut up-dasu! I, Musashi, will protect Sen-chan risking my life-dasu!
시끄러운 얘새끼!
What a noisy brat!
그만두오! 눈이 돌아가오!
Stop that-dasu! My eyes are spinning-dasu!
이럇!
Get lost!
무사시!
Musashi!
수상한 요술을 쓰는 놈! 이름을 대라!
A suspicious sorcery-using guy! Tell your anme!
츠바메가에시의 코지로인가. 나님은 이하 사천왕의 하나라 불리는 지라이얀!
You must be Kojirō, who is famous for Tsubamegaeshi. I am Jiraiyan, one of the Four Iga Kings!
지라이얀
Jiraiyan
지옥에 안내해 주마!
Let me lead you to the hell!
무슨! 비검! 츠바메가에시!
No way!
꽤 하는군, 코지로. 그러나 싸움은 지금부터다!
You're pretty good, Kojirō. But the fight begins now!
a vi ra hūṃ khaṃ, a vi ra hūṃ khaṃ, 화염포술!
a vi ra hūṃ khaṃ, a vi ra hūṃ khaṃ,
Flaming Cannonball Technique!
뭐야?!
What?!
당했다!
Damn!
꼴 좋다, 코지로!
Serves you right, Kojirō!
움직일 수가 없군!
I can't move!
센히메 님! 도망가 주십시오!
Senhime! Please run away!
코지로!
Kojirō!
빨리!
Hurry!
그래도...
But...
못 도망간다!
You're not running away!
이랴!
There!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
그만둬 주시오. 간지럽소.
Please stop-dasu. It tickles-dasu.
숨 막히오!
I can't breathe-dasu!
여긴...
Here is...
센짱!
Sen-chan!
네이놈, 보고 있소!
You bastard, I see you-dasu!
싫어싫어! 이거 놔!
No, no! Let me go!
오, 이걸로 한조 님께 막대한 보상을 받을 수 있겠어!
Yes! I'm going to receive a colossal reward from Lord Hanzo!
이랴!
There!
뭐뭐뭐, 뭐뭐뭐야! 뭐야!
Wh- what is this?! What's going on?!
-센짱!
-무사시!
-Sen-chan!
-Musashi!
너, 살아있었냐!
Were you alive?!
난 아직 죽을 수 없소!
I can't die yet-dasu!
a vi ra hūṃ khaṃ, 두꺼비의 거품, 방울배출술!
a vi ra hūṃ khaṃ, Toad Bubble, Bursting Technique!
이게 뭣이오!
What's this-dasu?!
이게 무슨, 딱딱해지오...
It's getting hard-dasu...
봤냐! 날 건드리면 그렇게 된다!
Did you see that? Hit me and that's what you get!
코지로, 괜찮아?
Kojirō, are you alright?
공주님, 면목이 없습니다.
I deeply apologize, princess.
빨리 무사시를 구해.
Hurry up and rescue Musashi.
알겠습니다.
Got it.
이걸 어째, 이걸...
What should I do with this?
그래!
That's it!
무사시! 원래대로 돌아왔구나!
Musashi! You're back!
뭐야?! 내 요술을 깨다니!
What the? You broke my black art?!
네이놈, 지라이얀! 이랴!
Jiraiyan, you bastard!
처벌해주겠다!
I will punish you!
케로키치!
Kerokichi!
네이놈, 무사시하고 코지로! 기억해둬라!
Musashi and Kojirō brats! Remember this!
-멈춰라!
-멈추시오!
-Stop!
-Stop right there!
집에 돌아가라!
Go back to home!
도망갔구나.
He ran away.
둘 다 무사해서 다행이야.
It's good to have you two safe.
센짱 덕분에 살았소!
I was rescued thanks to Sen-chan!
센히메 님이야말로 무사해서 다행입니다.
It is a relief that Senhime, you're safe.
코지로? 공주님이 아니라 센짱!
Kojirō? I told you not to call me princess - call me Sen-chan!
그게... 센님...
That's... Sen-dono...
지라이얀... 확실히 이하 사천왕이라 했나.
Jiraiyan... one of the Four Iga Kings, he said.
지라이얀의 요술을 깨다니 꽤 하는 애송이들이군.
Those brats are something, to break Jiraiyan's black arts.
그러나 내일은 목숨이 없을 줄 알아라!
But you will not have your life tomorrow!
음, 이렇게 베고 이렇게 해서 이렇게 되는 것이오...
Well, cut like this, and do that, and I get this-dasu...
그래도 센히메 님의 피리 부는 실력에는 놀랐습니다.
Anyway, I was truly surprised at Senhime's fluency of flute.
에도토피아 성 안에선 놀 상대가 없었어.
There was nobody to play with in Edotopia castle.
그래서 피리를 불면서 동물들하고 놀고 있었는데, 이렇게 쓰일 줄은 생각도 못 했어.
So I played with animals, playing my flute, and I didn't think I was going to play the flute for this purpose.
내리고 나서 이렇게 하오.
Pull it down and do this-dasu.
그리고 이렇게. 그리고 저렇게...
And this. And that...
아, 미안. 아니, 화났소?
Sorry. Uh, are you angry-dasu?
그만두오! 누가 살려주시오!
Stop that-dasu! Someone save me!
난폭한 말과 같은 센히메를 지키고 새신랑을 찾으러 가는 도중, 길에서 기다리는 건 비인가, 폭풍인가, 괴물인가!
What will be waiting for them, traveling to protect Senhime, who is like a raging horse, and to find a new husband? Will it be a rain, a storm, or a monster?
땀과 눈물의 사내의 여행, 가라, 무사시! 쭉 나아가라!
A journey of man full of sweat and tears. Advance, Musashi! Go ahead!
허공의 주머니에 달이
Sometimes the moon jumps over
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
the pocket of the empty sky
큰 소리로 웃으면
Laugh loudly and
내일에는 아침이 와
a morning will come tomorrow
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Don't care too much about losing
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
Keep doing! Go for it!
맨손은 강해
A bare hand is strong
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
That's how life is! Look, a chance
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
follows us wagging its tail!
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
That's how future also is! Look, tomorrow
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
여행 도중 만난 삼현금의 사내.
(Shamisen: three-stringed Japanese lute)
A guy with Shamisen that we met in our journey.
히카리노스케하고 여행하게 된 우리 앞에
Hikarinosuke has joined our journey, and in front of us,
사천왕의 하나, 오니히메가 츠치구모와 함께 덤벼들었소.
one of the Four Kings, Onihime came to attack us with Tsuchigumo-dasu.
츠치구모라고 하면, 환상의 명도를 지키는 괴물.
Tsuchigumo is a monster that protects the sword of a fantasy.
좋소! 내 이도류로 그 명도를 손에 넣어 보이겠소!
Alright! I'll take that sword with my dual blade skills-dasu!
다음 이야기! 미녀 오니히메 나타나오
Next story! Beautiful Woman Onihime Appears
질풍노도의 대활약을 보시오!
Watch the stormy big activities!
다음 이야기
미녀 오니히메 나타나오
기대하세요!
Next Episode
Beautiful Woman
Onihime Appears
Look forwards for it!